Margarethe Cammermeyer papers, 1963-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
Margarethe Cammermeyer papers
Bulk, 1991-2000
1963-2012
2186
UCLA Library Special Collections
26.0 linear ft. (59 document boxes, 2 record cartons, and 1 flat box)
Margarethe (Grethe) Cammermeyer was born in 1942 in Oslo, Norway. Her career as nurse in the military included distinguished service in Vietnam, work for the Veteran’s Administration, and a position as Chief Nurse of the Washington National Guard. As a result of her statement in an interview for top security clearance that she was a lesbian, she was separated from the military in 1992. She successfully challenged her discharge and the military’s regulations that mandated that lesbians and gay men be separated from the service. This experience, documented in her memoir, Serving in Silence, inspired her to become involved in LGBT activism and politics. The Margarethe Cammermeyer papers contain her personal, professional, and activist materials including correspondence, legal documents, photographs, videotapes, ephemera and other materials. The majority of the material relates to her successful challenge in the courts of both her discharge and the military’s regulations that mandated that lesbians and gay men be separated from the service between 1992 and 1997.
Cammermeyer, Margarethe, 1942-
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual materials must be digitized prior to use.
Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 7347666
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Margarethe Cammermeyer, 2013. This collection is part of an outreach and collection-building partnership between the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives, the UCLA Center for the Study of Women (CSW) and the UCLA Library.
Biography/History
Margarethe Cammermeyer was born on March 24, 1942 in Oslo, Norway. Her family immigrated to the United States in 1951, settling near Washington, D.C. She became an American citizen in 1960. From 1959 to 1963 she attended the University of Maryland, College Park, earning a Bachelors of Science in Nursing. In 1961, while at the University of Maryland, she joined the Army Student Nurse Program. Upon graduation in 1963, she reported for active duty, serving in United States Army Nursing Corps at Fort Sam Houston, Texas, Martin Army Hospital at Ft. Benning, Georgia, and a 2-year tour in Nuremberg, Germany. In Germany she married fellow soldier, Harvey Hawken, in 1965. At her request in 1967, she was sent to the 24th Evacuation Hospital at Long Binh, Vietnam where she served for 14 months as head nurse of a medical unit and of the neurosurgical intensive care unit. She was awarded a Bronze Star. She was forced to leave the military in 1968 when she became pregnant with the first of her four sons, as women were not permitted to have dependents.
After returning from Vietnam, she settled in Seattle, Washington with her family. She continued her work as a nurse and in 1971 began working at the Veterans’ Administration Hospital. She continued working in VA Medical Centers, including those in Seattle, San Francisco, and American Lake, until her retirement in 1996. She was honored as the Veterans’ Administration Nurse of the Year in 1985. She supplemented her appointment at the VA with part-time work as a lecturer and consultant. She also continued her studies, graduating from the University of Washington with Masters of Arts in Nursing in 1976 and a Ph.D. in Nursing Science in 1991. She divorced in 1980.
The military played an important role in her life. In 1972 when the regulation prohibiting women from serving with dependents she joined the Army Reserves, achieving the rank of Colonel in 1987. In 1988, she accepted the position of Chief Nurse of the Washington State National Guard. That same year she began a relationship with Diane Divelbess. In 1989, during an interview for top-secret clearance she told the interviewer, "I am a lesbian." As a result, she was separated from the military on June 1, 1992. On the same day, Lambda Legal and the Northwest Women’s Law Center filed suit on her behalf in Federal District Court in Seattle, challenging Cammermeyer’s discharge and the military’s regulations that mandated that lesbians and gay men be separated from the service. In June 1994, U.S. District Court Judge Thomas Zilly held that the ban on gays in the military violated the equal protection and due process guarantees of the U.S. Constitution and ordered the Army to reinstate Cammermeyer. She was reinstated in the Washington National Guard and resumed her position as Chief Nurse. The government did not appeal Cammermeyer’s right to be reinstated, but in its appeal asked the Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals to strike the judge’s ruling from the books. The ruling took issue with the older ban as well as new the “Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell” policy which was enacted in 1993. In October 1996, the Court of Appeals dismissed the government’s appeal as moot and denied the government’s request to vacate the district court’s ruling, sending the case back to the district court. In 1997 the district court denied the government’s motion to vacate, maintaining the value of the victory as precedent. In March 1997, Cammermeyer retired with full military privileges. She returned to health care work in 2006, opening an Adult Family Home to provide skilled care to the elderly. Since 2008, she has served as the Hospital Commissioner for Whidbey General Hospital.
Cammermeyer’s experiences with the military’s antigay policies inspired her to become involved in LGBT activism and politics. In 1994, she published a memoir, Serving in Silence; it was adapted into an Emmy winning television movie in 1995. Her first involvement in politics was in 1998 when she ran as a Democratic candidate for the United States Congress in Washington. Though she did not win the congressional seat, she continues to be involved in local politics, serving as the Chairperson of her local Democratic party. Between 1999 and 2001 she hosted the Grethe Cammermeyer Show, a daily internet talk show, on GAYBC Radio Network. She serves on the Military Advisory Council for the Servicemembers Legal Defense Network and the Defense Advisory Council of Women in the Services. Cammermeyer and her wife, artist Diane Dievelbess, have been involved in activism around a number of LGBT causes, including marriage equality. In 2012, after same-sex marriage was legalized in Washington, Cammermeyer and Divelbess became the first same-sex couple to get a marriage license in Island County.
Scope and Content
The Margarethe Cammermeyer papers contain her personal, professional, and activist materials including correspondence, legal documents, photographs, videotapes, ephemera, and other materials. The majority of the material is in the first series and relates to her successful challenge in the courts of both her discharge and the military’s regulations that mandated that lesbians and gay men be separated from the service between 1992 and 1997. A significant amount of materials in the second series documents her activism on LGBT issues, particularly in fighting discrimination against LGBT people in the military. This series contains copies of her memoir Serving in Silence and its film adaptation, correspondence, congressional campaign materials, photographs, writings, newspaper clippings, videotapes, audio cassettes, awards, and other materials relating to her professional life. The third series contains materials documenting her nursing career and personal life including a copy of dissertation, a yearbook, and wedding album.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Legal Papers, 1978-2008
Series 2: Professional Career and Activism, 1979-2011
Series 3: Personal Papers, 1963-2012
Series 1 is arranged according to its original order. Series 2 and 3 are arranged chronologically.
Related Material
DADT Digital Archive (http://dadtarchive.org/)
Dusty Pruitt Papers, 1945-2002. Coll 2012.029. ONE National Gay and Lesbian Archives
Cammermeyer, Margarethe, 1942-
Container List
- Series 1: Legal Papers., Bulk, 1991-1997.; 1978-2008.
  Scope and Content
  This series contains correspondence, briefs, depositions, exhibits, pleadings, reports, memoranda, transcripts, research materials, and other documents relating to Cammermeyer’s successful challenge of both her discharge and the military’s regulations that mandated that lesbians and gay men be separated from the service in the courts between 1992 and 1997. The materials provide detailed insights into Cammermeyer’s military career, the process of her separation from military service, and the strategies of her legal team. The materials were obtained from the files of her legal team of Perkins Coie, Lambda Legal, and Hedges and Caldwell.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  The video contained in this series must be digitized prior to use.
  - Rules and Regulations - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1978-1991. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Involuntary Separation Action Military Counsel/Respondent Packet - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1989-1991. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hearing Materials - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1989-1991. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits of Ralph Nutter - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1990-1994. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1991-1994. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Drafts 001- Memorandum in Opposition to Defendants' Motion for Judgement on the Pleadings - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1993. (Box 1)
  - Drafts 001- Memorandum in Opposition to Defendants' Motion for Judgement on the Pleadings - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1993. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Drafts 002- Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994-1997. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Drafts 002- Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994-1997. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Declaration of David M. Glass - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994 February 2. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Declaration of David M. Glass - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994 February 2. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cammermeyer Personal Documents - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1985-1995. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cammermeyer Personal Documents - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1985-1995. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Defendant's Response to Plaintiff's 1st - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 3)., 1991-1995. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Defendant's Response to Plaintiff's 1st - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 3)., 1991-1995. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Defendant's Response to Plaintiff's 1st - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 3)., 1991-1995. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Defendant's Response to Plaintiff's 1st - Perkins Coie Administrative (Folder 3) (1 of 3).., 1991-1995.. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Defendant's Response to Plaintiff's 1st - Perkins Coie Administrative (Folder 3) (2 of 3)., 1991-1995. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Defendant's Response to Plaintiff's 1st - Perkins Coie Administrative (Folder 3) (3 of 3)., 1991-1995. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Appellants' Motion for Reconsideration of Motion for Summary Disposition - Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit., 1995 April 21. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Consent Motion to Stay Briefing Schedule - Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit., 1995 April 21. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Brief for Appellants - Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit., 1995 June. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Brief for Amicus Curiae, Servicemembers Legal Defense Network in Support of Appellee and Plaintiff - Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit., 1995 August 17. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Background - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Background - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Documents - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Documents - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Department of Defense & Army National Guard and Army Reserve Policies on Homosexuality and Separation of Officers - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1992. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Defense Authorization Act & Authorizing Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1994 - Perkins Coie Administrative. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Related Cases - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 4)., 1991-1995. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Related Cases - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 4)., 1991-1995. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Related Cases - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 4)., 1991-1995. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Related Cases - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 4)., 1991-1995. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Deposition of General John P. Otjen - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994 February 16. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Deposition of General John P. Otjen - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994 February 16. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Deposition of General John P. Otjen - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1994 February 17. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits - Deposition of General John P. Otjen - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 4)., 1994 February 17. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits - Deposition of General John P. Otjen - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 4)., 1994 February 17. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits - Deposition of General John P. Otjen - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 4)., 1994 February 17. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits - Deposition of General John P. Otjen - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 4)., 1994 February 17. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Deposition of Admiral Thomas H. Moorer, (Ret.) - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1994 February 23. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Continued Deposition of Edwin Dorn - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1994 February 23. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Deposition of Oria S. Berndt - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1994 March 7. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Deposition of Robert L. Maginnis - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1994 February 25. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pleadings 001- Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1992-1993. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Pleadings 001- Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1992-1993. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pleadings 002- Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1993-1994. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pleadings 002- Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1993-1994. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pleadings 003- Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Pleadings 003- Cammermeyer v. Cheney - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Pleadings 001- Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Pleadings 001- Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Pleadings 002- Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Pleadings 002- Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Pleadings 003- Cammermeyer v. Perry - United States Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1995-1997. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Pleadings 007- Cammermeyer v. Cohen - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1997. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pleadings 007- Cammermeyer v. Cohen - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1997. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pleadings 004- Cammermeyer v. Perry - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pleadings 004- Cammermeyer v. Perry - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pleadings 005- Cammermeyer v. Perry - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Pleadings 005- Cammermeyer v. Perry - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pleadings 006 - Cammermeyer v. Perry - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994-1997. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Pleadings 006 - Cammermeyer v. Perry - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994-1997. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Listing of Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 4)., 1991. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Listing of Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 4)., 1991. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Listing of Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 4)., 1991. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Listing of Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 4)., 1991. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Crittendon Report Vol. III - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 4)., 1989 July. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Crittendon Report Vol. III - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 4)., 1989 July. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Crittendon Report Vol. III - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 4)., 1989 July. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Crittendon Report Vol. III - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 4)., 1989 July. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Crittendon Report - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1991. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Crittendon Report - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1991. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Transfer of Case Files - Perkins Coie Administrative., 2008. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 4)., 1992-1995. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 4)., 1992-1995. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 4)., 1992-1995. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 4)., 1992-1995. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 3)., 1994-1998. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 3)., 1994-1998. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 3)., 1994-1998. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - External Correspondence 001 - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1990-1992. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - External Correspondence 001 - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1990-1992. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - External Correspondence 002 - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1993. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - External Correspondence 002 - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1993. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - External Correspondence 003 - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - External Correspondence 003 - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - External Correspondence 004 - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - External Correspondence 004 - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - External Correspondence 005 - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1994. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - External Correspondence 005 - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1994. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - External Correspondence 006 - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1995-1997. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Original Briefs for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 6)., 1994. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Original Briefs for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 6)., 1994. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Original Briefs for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 6)., 1994. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Original Briefs for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 6)., 1994. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Original Briefs for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (5 of 6)., 1994. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Original Briefs for the 9th Circuit - Perkins Coie Administrative (6 of 6)., 1994. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 5)., 1988-1992. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 5)., 1988-1992. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 5)., 1988-1992. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 5)., 1988-1992. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (5 of 5)., 1988-1992. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 4)., 1990s. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 4)., 1990s. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 4)., 1990s. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 4)., 1990s. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 5)., 1994 February. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 5)., 1994 February. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 5)., 1994 February. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 5)., 1994 February. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (5 of 5)., 1994 February. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 6)., 1993-1994. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 6)., 1993-1994. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 6)., 1993-1994. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 6)., 1993-1994. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (5 of 6)., 1993-1994. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Plaintiff's Reply Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Summary Judgement - Perkins Coie Administrative (6 of 6)., 1993-1994. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1990s. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1990s. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 6)., 1990s. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 6)., 1990s. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (3 of 6)., 1990s. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (4 of 6)., 1990s. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (5 of 6)., 1990s. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Case Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (6 of 6)., 1990s. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Cammermeyer Documents - Exhibits - Service Record Volume I - Perkins Coie Administrative., 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Volume II - Federal Documents/Statements - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Volume II - Federal Documents/Statements - Perkins Coie Administrative (2 of 2)., 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Withdrawal of Federal Recognition Board - Volume III - Historical, Psychological, and Legal Research - Perkins Coie Administrative (1 of 2)., 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)